<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Ramon Morcillo</title>
    <link>https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Ramon Morcillo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL Hello World Server</title>
      <link>https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/graphql-hello-world-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/graphql-hello-world-server/</guid>
      <description>GraphQL Hello World Server The main purpose of this server-client Node.js project is to help other people understand how GraphQL exposes the data from the Server and the Client fetches it. I have tried to make it as simple as possible- if you want to dive into the code of the project you can find it here.
Now, straight to the point: GraphQL is a query language for APIs developed and open-sourced by Facebook to speed up the request process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visiting the Dolomites</title>
      <link>https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/visiting-dolomites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/visiting-dolomites/</guid>
      <description>What are the Dolomites? When I told people that I was going to or had been in the Dolomites they had no idea what they were, the truth is that I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know it until, a couple of years ago, my mother mentioned that she would like to visit them.
In short, the Dolomites is a mountain range that is part of the Alps. It is located in northern Italy in the provinces of Belluno, Bolzano, Trento, Udine and Pordenone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to protect your computer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/antivirus-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ramonmorcillo.com/blog/antivirus-free/</guid>
      <description>Install and renew ESET INTERNET SECURITY free With the intention of helping and teaching to install those people who need a quality antivirus, in this document I will explain how to install and renew for free the ESET INTERNET SECURITY antivirus in Windows, which is among the best in the market. If you are interested in buying it at the moment the price of the basic version of this antivirus is 30 euros in this link.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>